Heartbeats is a music, romance, drama film directed by Duane Adler.
When a bubbly American hip hop dancer goes to India with her family for a wedding, she is
impressed by a new dance style and falls in love with the man who introduced her to it.
Kelli Andrews, played by Krystal Ellsworth.
Aseem, played by Amitash Pradhan.
Deepika Zinta, played by Aneesha Joshi.
Michelle Andrews, played by Daphne Zuniga.
Richard Andrews, played by Paul McGillion.
Jae Juarez, played by Justin Chon.
Heartbeats is a 2017 romance-dance-dramedy written and
directed by Step Up creator Duane Adler.
The movie stars newcomers Krystal Ellsworth and Amitash Pradhan.
The film explores themes of dancing, sibling relationship, dance
competition, death of brother, intercultural relationship.
The tone is emotional.